Guide to the WCSU Office of University Publications & Design Records RG 7.3.2 RG 7.3.2
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Photographs
  - University Photographer's photo archive
    - CDs - Sep 2009-Oct 2009 (Box psa_89)
      Contains: 18 envelopes. Topics: football; MFA Art; men's soccer; alumni softball; Ives Family Fair; Men's Ice Hockey; Men's Rugby; field hockey; one book one community; "Mere Mortals" (play); substance abuse conference; volleyball; tailgating; first year experience conference; women's rugby; Jackie and Sean's wedding; Women's tennis; OBOC book discussion; race and law enforcement community panel discussion; women's soccer; football
    - CDs - Oct 2009-Dec 2009 (Box psa_90)
      Contains: 25 envelopes. Topics: 'A flea in her ear" ( play); women's basketball; take a kid to the game day; men's basketball; project homeless connect; winter wonderland; faculty tenure and promotion luncheon; jazz; HPX Internship fair; festival of trees; international education week; football; veteran's day; project clear; alumni; Guy Fawkes Day; "City of Angels" (play); Women's tennis; homecoming; scholarship reception; law-related education conference; Connecticut consortion for law and citizenship education
    - CDs - Jan 2010-Apr 2010 (Box psa_91)
      Contains: 57 envelopes. Topics: alumni scholarship dinner; nursing headshots; poetry; Bethel Middle School Science Fair; BOT Faculty Awards; WestConnect Anniversary Celebration; men's tennis; career fair; Warner Show Hanging (of pictures); Candlewood Lake; women's lacrosse; MFA art show; bridge program; womens center; legislative breakfast; Hubble event; men's lacrosse; WestConn Society Luncheon; Barnard Award; academic recognition ceremony; Veterans Lunch; WCSU Art Collections Show; bridge program; chamber music concert; big band concert; blue jeans for haiti; Dyko concert; women's basketball; NCAA 20th Reunion; employee of the semester; training for disabled adults; HSLP Cohort 2 training; sexuality counseling: children and families
    - CDs - Jan 2010-Apr 2010 (Box psa_92)
      Contains: 27 envelopes. Topics: men's lacrosse; nursing at Waterbury hospital; bridge program; third annual James Furman Honors recital; women's lacrosse; "A Flea in Her Ear" (play); women's basketball; LEC Championship; science horizon; WestConn Society; men's basketball; swimming senior day; scholarship recipient reception; women's basketball superfan event; swimming; basketball; Greenwald donation
    - CDs - Apr 2010-May 2010 (Box psa_93)
      Contains: 51 envelopes. Topics: intrepid aerial photography; WRD: western research day; bridge program; West Fest; men's tennis; Barnard Awards; SGA carnival; SPS convocation; nursing tea; employee of the semester; senior day: softball; jazz fest; psych awards; Gala; roots and shoots: arbor day; student leadership banquet; TKE jumpathon; Mario Masi Luncheon; Chinese Celebration; percussion ensemble concert; Hubble Week; science and tech fair; Khalda Logan Tribute; Anthropology club; archaeology forum; relay for life; bring your kid to work day; earth day; MSQ Haiti Charity concert; Future of Aerospace Round Table; B. Nemzer Symposium; "Magic Flute"; spring writing festival; world water day
    - CDs - Apr 2010-May 2010 (Box psa_94)
      Contains: 28 envelopes. Topics: undergraduate commencement; graduate commencement; men's tennis; multicultural fair; Ancel Convocation; Gala; Jazz Fest; men's rugby; men's baseball; women's lacrosse; Take your kid to work day; Roots and Shoots Earth Day; women's lacrosse; women's rugby; Macricosta Lecture Series; HPX Fair; men's lacrosse; "Magic Flute"; baseball; softball; men's tennis
    - CDs - May 2010-Aug 2010 (Box psa_95)
      Contains: 47 envelopes. Topics: weevil/milfoil research; flute camp; MFA writing workshop; college fair; bridges; writing camp; ConnCap; STEM summer experience; greenlight 3; animation camp; Connecticut science center; Newman Center; Reynard the Fox; greenlight academy: solar cars; the merry wives of Windsor; Ives Concert park; greenlight 2; Joe Namath Camp; greenlight; German students; Choices; Linda Vaden Goad Tree Dedication; Candlewood Lake: Weevil research training; Latino Festival; Diva Party; orientation; Abbott Tech Electrical Program; alumni spring weekend; senior research presentation
    - CDs - Jun 2010-Jul 2010 (Box psa_96)
      Contains: 27 envelopes. Topics: 'Best little whorehouse in Texas"; field hockey; football; cheerleading; dance team; women's soccer; homecoming; alumni golf #25; women's rugby; women's soccer; ice hockey; President to President scholarship; OBOC: The things they carried; "As Bees in Honey Drown" (play); Ives Family Fair; men's soccer; volleyball; 9/11 Memorial; gate ceremony; Ives Orchestra; Dukes of September; Campus improvements; "The Merry Wives of Windsor"; salamander habitat research; band camp; Moody Blues; USAF Band of liberty; science at night; Renaissance Festival
    - CDs - Aug 2010-Oct 2010 (Box psa_97)
      Contains: 46 envelopes. Topics: 'Best little whorehouse in Texas", football; weather conference; roots and shoots summit; entrepreneur of the year; Macricostas award; ice hockey; DFD Honors ceremony; banned books week; peace day; women's rugby team; women's tennis; golden circle lunch; foundation board; great hollow; field hockey; constitution day; women's soccer; gorilla environment theater; football; Kelley Bradley Scholarship; playfair; clubs carnival; bug adventure and rocketry; one book one community press conference; bridge program; Candlewood lake; youth volunteers
    - CDs - Oct 2010-Dec 2010 (Box psa_98)
      Contains: 46 envelopes. Topics: musical workshop; geriatric PE class; orchestra; jazz masterclass; faculty recognition program; diversity training; faculty member of the year; duct taped kid in student center; orchestra; Amahl; drag show; veteran's day; anti-war talk; JFK 50 exhibit; music educators conference; volleyball; Octoberfest jazz; education dissemination plan presentation; one book one community; homecoming; Fairfield tea; Namoli Brennet; Whitney Cummings; pizza with the president; 5k race; presidents club; PSI Matters; OBOC Vietnam food; project homeless; HPX internship fair
    - CDs - Nov 2010-Dec 2010 (Box psa_99)
      Contains: 5 envelopes. Topics: 'Amahl", basketball; wine tasting; nursing career fair; ghost at night; LEC Final; soccer
    - CDs - Jan 2011-Apr 2011 (Box psa_100)
      Contains: 78 envelopes. Topics: jazzfest; CSUS assessment conference; connecticut counseling association conference; academic day; alumni association scholarship; grad profiles;roots and shoots earth day; take your kid to work day; cyber bullying; prometheus chamber music; women's lacrosse; men's tennis; MBA student presentation; black and white poetry reading; JLA honors class; cabaret; animal week; spring writing festival; civil war; employee of the month; softball; building improvements; relay for life; Danbury Public Schools Invention Convention; "I Love a Piano"; student dorms; biggest loser; women's history month; barnard award; Pi Day; NYC honors program; Loni Love; Science/ Toyota TAP Project; black history month; ice hockey; brown bag lunch; videography; women's basketball; MFA art; swimming; Kenosia presentation; Diving; snow; HSLP; "Three Sisters"; alumni day
    - CDs - May 2011-Aug 2011 (Box psa_101)
      Contains: 54 envelopes. Topics: commencement; SGA carnival; athletic banquet; Suessical; student leadership banquet; CSUS research day; career fair; "Street Scenes" (opera); baseball; men's lacrosse; WestConn society Luncheon; CT ballet; Steely Dan concert; "I Love a Piano"; "Earth, Wind, and Fire"; Frampton; undergrad commencement; JLA honors program; men's lacrosse; women's basketball; men's basketball; "Three Sisters"; Jazz; LEC; men's basketball; Credence (play); womens center counseling; west fest; multicultural fair; Danbury fire department drills; "Fantastic Mr. Fox" (play); WRD; Barnard Awards; zombie walk; softball; garden club; tennis; men's lacrosse; revolutionary movements talk; nursing tea; SPS convocations; Ancell Convocation
    - CDs - Aug 2011-Oct 2011 (Box psa_102)
      Contains: 24 envelopes. Topics: football; women's basketball senior day; Namath; math and science academy; homecoming; "Sweeney Todd" (musical); school of visual and performing arts; field hockey; women's soccer; volleyball; Roberts Avenue School chimney knockdown
    - CDs - Jun 2011-Dec 2011 (Box psa_103)
      Contains: 115 envelopes. Topics: sweetheart circle; men's basketball; project homeless connect; Amahl (play); HPX internship fair; Dong Lin; "A Christmas Carol"; holiday wine tasting; John Patitucci; Jazz masterclass; women's basketball; debate team; dorm rooms; international education week; veterans day; Sweeney Todd; popular culture conference; Being Home (veterans event); music educators workshop; emergency shelter; "In it to win it" (career event); speed networking; senior research group; volleyball; hoodwinked; health fair; Doug Fine; Danbury's Ecological History (panel discussion); men's soccer; chili cookoff; interview with Alexander Sawchyn; tennis; supreme court; Danbury fire department community day; Women's rugby; Sweeney Todd; ice hockey; Jane Roberts lunchtime talk; Danbury Hospital; field hockey; alumni ice hockey; Tibetan medicine workshop; dance class; HPX wellness; Jungle Red; honors pizza party; women's center walk to end domestic violence; alumni golf; Danbury high school class of 1961; tree dedication; fashion fights cancer; Dan Goble; Fernando Bermudez; peace day; men's soccer; golden circle; constitution day; WCSU foundation; hurricane Irene; playfair; Great Hollow; OBOC press conference; Gong show; RA training; Connecticut science center; Beach Boys (band); MFA writing; flute camp; young writers; ConnCap; STEM camp dissection; Ives Family Orchestra; string camp; WXCI; summer youth college fair; alumni marketplace; Joe Namath football camp; Archaeological dig; observatory; president to president scholarship; freshmen orientation
    - CDs - Jan 2012-Sep 2012 (Box psa_104)
      Contains: 166 envelopes. Topics: STEM camp; ConnCap; reggae fest; bridge program; VPA (visual and performin arts) construction; chamber of commerce event; JC Barone videography; Bolivia trip; orientation; Danbury fire department regional rescue training; president's club; athletic banquet; world research day; campus day; baseball senior day; SPS convocation; jazz fest; men's basketbal; "Be the change": Honors Sudan lecture; LETRA Poetry Reading: alumni Association scholarship goup photo; Barnard Awards; HPX healthcare; lacrosse; creativity and compassion conference; nursing alumni event; grad profiles; animal week; men's lacrosse; webisode festival and luncheon; MFA art; social work; women's center; nursing tea; softball; KUKK; men's tennis; education administration panel cohort; career fair; smart board training; world language lecture; WestConn society luncheon; academically adrift lecture; "My road to WestConn" lecture series; Candlewood Valley Nursing Home; GSA protest; gay/straight alliance; women's history month: sex trade; Ghana visit; black history month; Hat City debate; "Carmen" ( opera); ice hockey;admissions; O'Neill Center; Gymnastics Revolution; Jazz students; women's swimming senior day; imaginary; head shots (theater, basketball); Sweeney Todd; Lysistrata (play); Lobsang Sangay ( prime minister of tibet);women's alumni basketball; Mission of mercy dental clinic; garden series; women's soccer; golden circle; legacy group; "Major Barbara" (play); Ancell Day; Ives Festival orchestra; country music; scavenger hunt; clubs carnival; Reckfest; Playfair; Straight No Chaser; volleyball; bridge program; football; markeplace; Daughtry; radio station promo; meet and greet; alumni clock; golden dragon: Chinese acrobats; Beatle Fest; Danbury Fields Forever; music camp carnival; STEM camp; puppet show; Connecticut ballet; robots; Band camp; ConnCap Jeopardy; school house rocks; jazz faculty concert; young writers camp; summer string camp
    - CDs - Sep 2012-Apr 2013 (Box psa_105)
      Contains: 156 envelopes. Topics: undergraduate art; alice in wonderland (play); HPX internship; hancock scholarship luncheon; campus day; Barnard awards; Roots and Shoots; grad profiles; webisode: men's lacrosse; Praxair scholarship; Zac and Taylor's Autism Panel; Choral performance; softball; celebration of abolition; MFA art; Animal week; women's lacrosse; compassion conference; career fair; dialogs of the carmelites; SVPA; baseball; education conference; relay for life; O'Neill Center; women's lacrosse; Sandy Hook fundraiser; softball; career fair workshop; "Prove it" day; men's lacrosse; men's tennis; career development center; JC Barone videography; Ives donor reception; ice hockey banquet; Stardom, Sexuality, and Hollywood: Nazi Germany; women's history month; HPX health fair; Tuition hike protest; Pi day; women's month; Barnard Award; one billion rising; academic recognition ceremony; New York philharmonic; Nicholas Pappas: Greek lecture; break the chain (play); Jame Furman honors recital; bridge program; flash mob; Roger Sherman debate society; spring awakening (play); smart board training; united way dinner; gun control conference; presidents' day lecture; LEC women's basketball; Grimes retrospective art show; WXCI reunion; SVPA; HSLP internship; snow; MFA art; country kids; anthropology/archaeology; bridge program; white out; admissions; play it by ear; homecoming; fuel cell installation; swimming and diving; student headshots; basketball; "A tribute to Newtown"; WCSU police toy drive for Department of Children and Families; IA event; institutional advancement; Amahl (opera); concert choir; "Into the woods" (musical); jazz masterclass; football coaches' headshots; music and theater workshop; international education week; new basketball floor; CFFIS: Body language lecture; Danbury fire department training; veteran's day ceremony; election collection; charm school; women's soccer; volleyball; men's soccer; dance team; cheerleading; fall foliage; field hockey; His Holiness the Dalai Lama (HHDL) day; Sand Mandala; chanting; weather conference; homecoming; cabaret; Candlewood canal race; marketing club; "Major Barbara"; one book one community; 5k campus to campus; zombie fest; campus police department swearing in; annual entrepreneurs luncheon; alumni golf at Ritcherd park; wounded warriors project; Greek theater "Helen of Troy"; compassion in motion: scroll signing (Dalai Lama); aquatic plants class; roots and shoots: international peace day
    - CDs - Apr 2013-Dec 2013 (Box psa_106)
      Contains: 163 envelopes. Topics: homecoming; football; volleyball; tennis; soccer; bonfire; vet training program; athletics senior days; field hockey; ice hockey; financial aid day; 5k run (campus to campus); high school choral festival; entrepreneur of the year; roots and shoots; feminism project; sigma chi; "Two nights near Doolin" (theater); KUKK; fall colors; majors fair; wounded warrior project; HPX internship; alumni golf; NEASE visit; poetry reading; one hundred thousand poets to end violence; music therapy; HPX students; Ancell Mentor reception; HPX internship; social work conference; math emporium; project homeless connect; ice hockey; JLA adjunct breakfast; holiday party; tree lighting; childcare center and womens' center: bullying puppet show; athletics; jazz masterclass; international education week; trees for troops; TEDX Conference; cheerleaders; dance team; VPA building; financial literacy workshop; veterans' day; foliage; addiction conference (by Choices); institution advancement; Bridge program; election connection; Plonia Nixon Gallery lecture; "Chicago" dress rehearsal; homecoming; class of 1963: 50th reunion; HSLP meeting; Greeks rush; Ives Festival Orchestra; SGA clubs carnival; smart board training; Gate ceremony; alumni legacy; Playfair; bridge program; Bethel middle school; entrepreneur of the year; compassion action network; string music camp; Tony Bennett;annual case writers workshop; Alice in Wonderland; Senator Blumenthal; German students (from Germany); centennial scholarship; centennial circle; government arts award; New Haven Arts and Ideas festival; alumni cocktail social; Lysistrata (play); WTBY nursing graduation; Western Research Day; badminton; TKE Jumpathon; Ancell Convocations; national gun victims action council; chuck's mini mudder; jazzfest; WestFest; Tough Mudder; field day; nursing honors convocation; campus shots; student leadership banquet; student athletics banquets; student athletics banquet; mental health conference; archaeological site; west side campus; alumni NYC cruise; math conference; Danbury fire department: volunteer fire companies; undergrad commencement; memorial day parade